{
    "id": "713f066c37f94a219b92235c278816e3",
    "title": "While And During | Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I met James ………………. my holiday in Japan.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "during",
                "while"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I injured my leg ……………….. playing football.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "during",
                "while"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I learnt French ……………. I was working in a museum in Paris.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "while",
                "during"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "It happened ……………. they were sleeping.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "while",
                "during"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "We had a discussion ………………… the lunchbreak.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "during",
                "while"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Something interesting happened ………………… my stay in Canada.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "during",
                "while"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "People suffered a lot of hardships ……………. the floods.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "during",
                "while"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I fell asleep …………….. I was watching the film.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "while",
                "during"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I fell asleep ……………. the service.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "while",
                "during"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "……………….. living in Rome, I met some really interesting people.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "While",
                "During"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}